{
  "Lesson1": [
    { "question": "Which one means 'I'?", "options": ["Yo", "En", "es", "en"], "answer": "Yo", "answered": false},
    { "question": "Which one means 'am'?", "options": ["Yo", "En", "soy", "es"], "answer": "soy", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which one means 'is'?", "options": ["Yo", "En", "soy", "es"], "answer": "es", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which one means 'in'?", "options": ["Yo", "En", "soy", "es"], "answer": "En", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which one means 'Spanish'?", "options": ["el", "Espanol", "ella", "yo"], "answer": "Espanol", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which one means 'he'?", "options": ["el", "Espanol", "ella", "yo"], "answer": "el", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which one means 'she'?", "options": ["el", "Espanol", "ella", "yo"], "answer": "ella", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'I am in Spanish'?", "answer": "Yo soy en espanol", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'He is in Spanish'?", "answer": "Ella es en espanol", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'Ella es en espanol'?", "answer": "She is in Spanish", "answered": false }
  ],

  "Lesson2": [
    { "question": "Which country speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Portugal", "Mexico", "China", "Japan"], "answer": "Mexico", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which country speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Spain", "Brazil", "India", "France"], "answer": "Spain", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which country speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Venezuela", "Vietnam", "Russia", "Nigeria"], "answer": "Venezuela", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which country doesn’t speak Spanish?", "options": ["Mexico", "Portugal", "Venezuela", "Spain"], "answer": "Portugal", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which country doesn’t speak Spanish?", "options": ["Columbia", "El Salvador", "Equatorial Guinea", "Sweden"], "answer": "Sweden", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which country doesn’t speak Spanish?", "options": ["Nicaragua", "Argentina", "Panama", "Singapore"], "answer": "Singapore", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Which is the only African country that speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Equatorial Guinea", "Madagascar", "Egypt", "Chad"], "answer": "Equatorial Guinea" },
    { "question": "Name the only country that speaks Spanish in North America.", "answer": "Mexico", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Name the only country that speaks Spanish in Europe.", "answer": "Spain", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How many countries speak Spanish?", "answer": "21 countries", "answered": false }
  ],

  "Lesson3": [
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'I' with AR verbs?", "options": ["a", "as", "amos", "o"], "answer": "o", "answered": false },
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'you' with AR verbs?", "options": ["a", "as", "amos", "o"], "answer": "as", "answered": false },
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'he' with AR verbs?", "options": ["a", "as", "amos", "o"], "answer": "a", "answered": false },
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'we' with AR verbs?", "options": ["a", "as", "amos", "o"], "answer": "amos", "answered": false },
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'you' with ER/IR verbs?", "options": ["es", "an", "imos", "en"], "answer": "es", "answered": false },
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'them' with ER/IR verbs?", "options": ["e", "an", "imos", "en"], "answer": "en", "answered": false },
    { "question": "What is the verb conjugation for 'he' with ER/IR verbs?", "options": ["e", "an", "imos", "en"], "answer": "e", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Correct conjugation for 'them' using AR verbs?", "answer": "an", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Correct conjugation for 'we' using ER verbs?", "answer": "emos", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Correct conjugation for 'we' using IR verbs?", "answer": "imos", "answered": false }
  ],

  "Lesson4": [
    { "question": "How do you say 'to eat' in Spanish?", "options": ["comer", "beber", "tener", "ir"], "answer": "comer", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'to drink' in Spanish?", "options": ["comer", "beber", "tener", "ir"], "answer": "beber", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'milk' in Spanish?", "options": ["leche", "agua", "hamburguesa", "manzanas"], "answer": "leche", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'water' in Spanish?", "options": ["leche", "agua", "hamburguesa", "manzanas"], "answer": "agua", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'apple' in Spanish?", "options": ["leche", "agua", "hamburguesa", "manzanas"], "answer": "manzanas", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'hamburguesa' in English?", "options": ["milk", "water", "hamburger", "apple"], "answer": "hamburger", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'agua' in English?", "options": ["milk", "water", "hamburger", "apple"], "answer": "water", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Translate: 'I drink water' into Spanish.", "answer": "Yo bebo agua", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Translate: 'I eat apples' into Spanish.", "answer": "Yo como manzanas", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Translate: 'El come hamburguesas' into English.", "answer": "He eats hamburgers", "answered": false }
  ],

  "Lesson5": [
    { "question": "How do you say 'to clean' in Spanish?", "options": ["lavar", "limpiar", "mirar", "abrir"], "answer": "limpiar", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'to open' in Spanish?", "options": ["lavar", "limpiar", "mirar", "abrir"], "answer": "abrir", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'to wash' in Spanish?", "options": ["lavar", "limpiar", "mirar", "abrir"], "answer": "lavar", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'to watch' in Spanish?", "options": ["lavar", "limpiar", "mirar", "abrir"], "answer": "mirar", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'door' in Spanish?", "options": ["puerta", "platos", "peliculas", "cama"], "answer": "puerta", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'plates' in Spanish?", "options": ["puerta", "platos", "peliculas", "cama"], "answer": "platos", "answered": false },
    { "question": "How do you say 'bed' in Spanish?", "options": ["puerta", "platos", "peliculas", "cama"], "answer": "cama", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Translate: 'I wash the plate' into Spanish.", "answer": "Yo llavo el plato", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Translate: 'I open the door' into Spanish.", "answer": "Yo abro la puerta", "answered": false },
    { "question": "Translate: 'El limpia la cama' into English.", "answer": "He cleans the bed", "answered": false }
